# Jyothi Mani R

# Cloud Architect



www.linkedin.com/in/jyothimani



+91 9791109009



Jyothimani1197@gmail.com



User

Cloud Architect with a focus on AWS solutions, holding the **Solutions Architect Associate SAA-CO3** certification. Possessing 2.7 years of dedicated involvement in cloud computing within the FireTV team, where responsibilities included the creation, ingestion, identification, troubleshooting, and maintenance of the FireTV Catalog. Instrumental in contributing to the analysis, development, testing, and deployment of small-scale ACES automation. Eager to apply my extensive expertise and skills to excel in a challenging role as a Cloud Architect.



Work Experience



Mphasis (Foreign language officer - Deutsch) Dec 2022 - Jul 2023

Engaged with Swedish Fintech Company, where my sole responsibility is to communication with customers located in Germany, Austria, Switzerland and merchants via email and telephone channels to assist their queries. In addition to offering comprehensive assistance to customers and resolving inquiries, a significant component of my role entails proficient translation between German and English.



### Amazon (Catalog Analyst)

Feb 2020 - Aug 2022

- Collaborating with business partners to create a personalized Catalog in FireTv.
- Creating a secure environment for the Content Catalog in AWS S3 bucket and maintaining it without any duplication or overlapping.
- · Conducting adequate Catalog Integration Testing, Judgments, VMT (Vocabulary management tool) and **MHOWLS** for quality assurance and good customer experience.
- Perform LAT (Live App Testing) to check the behavior of the Application, troubleshoot bugs in FireTV Devices and fix it.
- Perform Daily live and Weekly live Deeplinking to ensure buy box winning and contents playing without interruption of any external credentials.
- Mapping Catalog contents with appropriate IMDB rating and with other third party providers in Combee Match Editor.
- Responsible for handling external S3 tickets, MCM (Modelled Change Management), Spy Onboarding, **G2S2 Onboarding** tickets in EN and DE market places.

accesshealthcare Access Healthcare (AR Client Partner)

Jun 2019 - Jan 2020

- Review CMS 1500 (Professional claim) and check the status by calling the payer or through IVR /Web Portal and handling inbound calls.
- Maintaining both corporate and consumer accounts and keep within credit terms and lines. Maintain strict patient confidentiality according to HIPAA regulations



#### Omega Healthcare (AR Associate - HFRI) Dec 2018 - Jun 2019

- Review UB04 (Hospital Claim) of Medicaid, managed care, hospice, BCBS and UHC. Maintaining records by microfilming invoices, debits, and credits.
- Working with collections personnel to verify the status of delinquent accounts and solicit payments on overdue accounts. Posted payments and make adjustments to accounts and analyze credit accounts for refunds.



#### Education

College-KCS (Bachelor of Science, Computer science - 72%)

April 2018

Higher secondary school - Victory (73.4166667%)

April 2015

Senior Secondary School - Velammal Vidyalaya (8.8 CGPA points)

April 2013



#### Mílestones

- AWS solutions architect associate certificate.
- Initiated, Developed and Deployed a total of 5 Kaizen Projects which contributed to a total Annual Save of \$24.38K.
- Achieved "Raising beyond the Bar" ranking in Annual Review 2021-2022 by contributing 4 Kaizen and 8 JDI small scale automations.
- Rewarded with "Mountain Mover" for a total of 5 Months for maintaining a productivity above 130% and "Excellence in Quality "for 2 months for maintaining 100% quality which contributed to win the "Team of the Quarter "in 2022.
- Awarded for exclusive contribution to Live Events and Pre Launch Request.



## Language Proficiency



English - Fluent (YLE Flyers Certified from University of Cambridge)



Deutsch - Advance (C1.2 certification from Goethe Max Mueller Bhavan)



Tamíl - Native speaker



## Specialties

Cloud - AWS / kubernetes / Docker

Programming Language - Python / Django / pycharm / Anaconda

OS - Linux

Certification – AWS Solutions Architect Associate

https://github.com/jyothimani



Iyothi Mani